realtree.com 2010-06-23

# Realtree: Privacy

## PRIVACY POLICY

At Realtree.com, we know how concerned you are with how information about you is used and shared, and we are glad that you trust us to handle your information responsibly. This notice explains our Privacy Policy. When you visit Realtree.com, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this policy.

#### Information Gathered

We receive and store any information you enter on the Realtree.com web site, or you give us by any other means. You can choose not to provide us with certain information that we request, but by doing so, you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features, such as contests or giveaways.

We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, submission of materials, photos, etc. and/or site registrations.

If you desire that your personal information disclosed by you on this Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. web site not be rented, sold, or exchanged or that you not receive any future solicitations from Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. related to the information you disclose on this Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. web site send an email request to Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. at the address listed below. Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. web site participants must be aware that when they disclose personal information on bulletin boards, through hot links or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties receiving your information.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. Please provide us with your correct phone number.

If you provide us with your credit card number, the credit card number is only used for purchasing Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. products, memberships, and any other services that may be offered by Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. If a credit card number is transmitted to Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. or its affiliates for the purchase of Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. products, memberships, or any other services offered by Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. such number is encrypted and verified through a reputable SSL when transmitted to Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd. or its affiliates.

#### “Cookies” and How We Use Them

We also receive and store certain types of information automatically when you interact with us. For example, like many other web sites, we use “cookies”, and we obtain some information when your web browser accesses Realtree.com.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our system to recognize your browser, and to provide certain other features.

#### Remember to Log Off

You must be careful not to inadvertently allow access to your information. In the event that you use a public or shared computer, be sure to log off when you are finished. This warning is for your protection. By logging off, you deny access to any of your information that you may have provided to Realtree.com.

#### Children’s Privacy

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000, and imposes certain requirements on Web sites directed at children under 13 that collect information on those children, and on Web sites that know they are collecting information on children under 13. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our Web site. No one under the age of 15 should submit any personal information without the consent of a parent or guardian. In addition, unless expressly stated in connection with a particular promotion, our online sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who are at least 18.

#### Electronic Communications

When you visit Realtree.com or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

#### Further Information

If you would like further information or have any questions about our privacy policy, you may contact us at the following address:  
Jordan Outdoor Enterprises Ltd.  
1390 Box Circle  
Columbus, GA 31907

* * *

» Top
